[{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980267976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":24620,"timeElapsed":92649},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980278200,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":10223,"timeElapsed":102873},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980284720,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":6519,"timeElapsed":109393},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980290520,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":5799,"timeElapsed":115193},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980299992,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":9471,"timeElapsed":124665},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980305896,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":5903,"timeElapsed":130569},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980309264,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3368,"timeElapsed":133937},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980319080,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":9815,"timeElapsed":143753},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980321551,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2471,"timeElapsed":146224},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980342455,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":20063,"timeElapsed":167128},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980346319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":3863,"timeElapsed":170992},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980353367,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":7047,"timeElapsed":178040},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980357296,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3928,"timeElapsed":181969},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980365143,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":7847,"timeElapsed":189816},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980370391,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":5247,"timeElapsed":195064},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980375159,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":4768,"timeElapsed":199832},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980380583,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":5423,"timeElapsed":205256},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980384959,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"155","question":"What was your first impression of your current home town or city the first time you ever visited? If you were born where you currently live, describe how others often find it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4375,"timeElapsed":209632},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980395791,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":9503,"timeElapsed":220464},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980400383,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":4591,"timeElapsed":225056},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980406055,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":5671,"timeElapsed":230728},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980411615,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":5559,"timeElapsed":236288},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980414407,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2791,"timeElapsed":239080},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980417263,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2855,"timeElapsed":241936},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980430503,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":13240,"timeElapsed":255176},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980435175,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":4671,"timeElapsed":259848},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980440287,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5112,"timeElapsed":264960},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980445158,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"102","question":"How are you ACTUALLY doing these days?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":4871,"timeElapsed":269831},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980456854,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":10719,"timeElapsed":281527},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980461550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":4695,"timeElapsed":286223},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980465166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3615,"timeElapsed":289839},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980467382,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2215,"timeElapsed":292055},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980471142,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3759,"timeElapsed":295815},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980474294,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3151,"timeElapsed":298967},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980480246,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":5951,"timeElapsed":304919},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980486806,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":6559,"timeElapsed":311479},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980492046,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5240,"timeElapsed":316719},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980502222,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":9095,"timeElapsed":326895},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980506534,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4311,"timeElapsed":331207},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980514230,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":7695,"timeElapsed":338903},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980524254,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":10023,"timeElapsed":348927},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980529870,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":5615,"timeElapsed":354543},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980533710,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":3839,"timeElapsed":358383},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980536654,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2943,"timeElapsed":361327},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980541510,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4856,"timeElapsed":366183},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980547334,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"205","question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":5823,"timeElapsed":372007},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980551694,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Open your phone and pull up a recent photo you took. Describe what is happening in this photo.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4359,"timeElapsed":376366},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980560454,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":7847,"timeElapsed":385127},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980565742,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":5287,"timeElapsed":390415},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980569917,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4175,"timeElapsed":394590},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980574909,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4991,"timeElapsed":399582},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980581149,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":6239,"timeElapsed":405822},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980585429,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":4279,"timeElapsed":410102},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980588198,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2767,"timeElapsed":412871},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980594037,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":5839,"timeElapsed":418710},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980596557,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"69","question":"Do you like to travel? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":2519,"timeElapsed":421230},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980603486,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":6080,"timeElapsed":428159},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980606157,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":2671,"timeElapsed":430830},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980609909,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3752,"timeElapsed":434582},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980614381,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4471,"timeElapsed":439054},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980621773,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":7391,"timeElapsed":446446},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980624141,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2367,"timeElapsed":448814},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980627565,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3423,"timeElapsed":452238},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980632333,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":4767,"timeElapsed":457006},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980634765,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"132","question":"What was the best advice someone ever gave you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2431,"timeElapsed":459438},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980649013,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":13023,"timeElapsed":473686},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980654045,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5032,"timeElapsed":478718},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980663509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":9463,"timeElapsed":488182},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980671653,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":8143,"timeElapsed":496326},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980674893,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3240,"timeElapsed":499566},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980678405,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3511,"timeElapsed":503078},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980683277,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":4871,"timeElapsed":507950},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980687820,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":4543,"timeElapsed":512493},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980690436,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2615,"timeElapsed":515109},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980703700,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":12319,"timeElapsed":528373},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980707188,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3487,"timeElapsed":531861},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980710716,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3527,"timeElapsed":535389},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980712996,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2279,"timeElapsed":537669},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980721500,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":8503,"timeElapsed":546173},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980725652,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":4152,"timeElapsed":550325},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980729844,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":4191,"timeElapsed":554517},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980739156,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":9311,"timeElapsed":563829},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980743668,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4511,"timeElapsed":568341},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980755460,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":10855,"timeElapsed":580133},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980761420,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":5959,"timeElapsed":586093},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980769012,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":7592,"timeElapsed":593685},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980774956,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":5943,"timeElapsed":599629},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980777492,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2535,"timeElapsed":602165},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980781684,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4191,"timeElapsed":606357},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980785180,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":3495,"timeElapsed":609853},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980790676,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":5495,"timeElapsed":615349},{"subjectID":"3vuse0u6pw","prolificID":"6682f7019ea9bcdd2e3f1394","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23a1bc42e3cec77c6b7","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980798740,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"127","question":"Who, if anyone, would you totally uproot your life for and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":8063,"timeElapsed":623413}]